Inventory of the James A. Bill Papers 1940-2003
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Collection of Iran Material, 1975-2004, bulk 1984-2003
  - Journals and Newsletters on Middle Eastern Issues including Iran (1)
    - (1, 12)
      - Society of Iranian Studies Newsletters 1987 - 1995 (1, 12, 2)
        - (1, 12, 2)
          - S.I.S. Newsletter: A Publication of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 19. No. 3. Autumn 1987 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 20. No.1. Winter/Spring 1988. (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 20. No. 2. Spring/Summer 1988 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 20. No. 3. Fall 1988 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 21. No. 1. Winter 1989 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 21. No. 2. Spring/Summer 1989. (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 21. No. 3. Fall 1989 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 22. No. 1. Winter 1990 (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 22. No. 2. Spring/Summer 1990. (1, 12, 2)
          - The Society for Iranian Studies Newsletter. Vol. 22. No. 3. Fall 1990 (1, 12, 2)
          - SIS News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 23. No. 1. Fall 1991 (1, 12, 2)
          - S.I.S. News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 22. No. 2. Spring 1991. (1, 12, 2)
          - S.I.S. News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 24. No.1. Fall 1992 (1, 12, 2)
          - S.I.S. News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 23. No. 2. Spring 1992 (1, 12, 2)
          - SIS News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 25. No. 1. Summer 1994 (1, 12, 2)
          - SIS News: The Newsletter of the Society for Iranian Studies. Vol. 25. No. 2. Winter 1995 (1, 12, 2)
          - Memorandum from the Society for Iranian Studies: concerning S.I.S. Conference. 11/1/1992 (1, 12, 2)
        Subseries 3: SERMIESS (Southeast Regional Middle East and Islamic Studies Seminar) Newsletters 1989 - 1994
      - SERMIESS (Southeast Regional Middle East and Islamic Studies Seminar) Newsletters 1989 - 1994 (1, 12, 3)
        - (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 11. No. 2. Spring 1994 (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from John Parcels to SERMEISS members. Subject: Fall Meeting, etc. (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 10. No. 2. Spring 1993o SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 10. No. 2. Spring 1993 (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 6. No. 1. Fall 1988 (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from Ronald A. Messier, to SERMIESS members. Subject: Season Greetings, newsletter, and dues (1, 12, 3)
            - Dues Sheet (1, 12, 3)
          - Letter to SERMIESS members concerning fall meeting. 8/27/1989 (1, 12, 3)
            - Reservation Form (1, 12, 3)
            - Map to Valle Crucis Mission School Conference Center (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol 6. No. 2. Spring 1989 (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 7. No. 1. Fall 1989 (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Program for Spring Meeting with map on the back (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from SERMIESS from Ron Messier to Members. Subject: Several Items of Business. 1/26/1990 (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 7. No. 2. Spring 1990 (1, 12, 3)
          - Letter from James Bill. 10/26/1990 (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from Ron Messier to SERMIESS members. Subject: fall meeting. 8/17/1990 (1, 12, 3)
          - SERMIESS Program for Fall Meeting. 9/28 - 30/1990. Valle Cruis, NC. (1, 12, 3)
          - Letter from Don Reid to James Bill. 4/16/1990: Invitation to SERMIESS fall meeting (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from James Bill. 9/3/1990 (1, 12, 3)
            - Reservation form for SERMIESS meeting (1, 12, 3)
          - Ellen - Fairbanks Bodman (film consultant), Ron Bartholomew (no print manager). Middle East and Islamic World Filmography 1990. Nonprint Materials Collection. R.B. House Library, University of North Carolina. (1, 12, 3)
          - Information sheet for SERMIESS Newsletter: Signed by James Bill in affiliation with Reeves Center for International Relations at the College of William and Mary (1, 12, 3)
          - Map to Valle Cruis Mission School Conference Center (1, 12, 3)
          - Pamphlet: Southeast Regional Middle East and Islamic Studies Seminar. SERMIESS. Middle Tennessee State University: Murfreesboro, TN (1, 12, 3)
            - Memorandum from Ron Messier to SERMEISS Members. Subject: Spring Meeting, etc. 2/8/1991 (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Program outline Spring 1991: 4/12 - 14 at Savannah, Georgia (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS map to Armstrong State College in Savannah, Georgia (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 8. No. 1. Fall 1990 (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Application form (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS invoice. 2/8/1991 (1, 12, 3)
          - Memorandum from John Parcels to SERMIESS members. Subject: Spring meeting, etc. (1, 12, 3)
            - Program for Spring Meeting. 3/19 - 21/1993. Old Dominion University, Norfolk, Virginia (1, 12, 3)
            - Map of Hampton Roads Area (1, 12, 3)
            - SERMIESS Newsletter. Vol. 10. No. 1. Fall 1992 (1, 12, 3)
        Subseries 4: U.S. Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations 1993 - 1995
      - U.S. Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations 1993 - 1995 (1, 12, 4)
        - (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 3, No. 1. January 1995 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 5. June - July 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 3. March 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 4. April - May 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 3. March 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 2. February 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 2, No. 1. January 1994 (1, 12, 4)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 1, No. 9. December 1993 (1, 12, 4)
        Subseries 5: U.S. Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations 1993
      - U.S. Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations 1993 (1, 12, 5)
        - (1, 12, 5)
          - Two Copies: U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 1, No. 8. November 1993 (1, 12, 5)
          - Two Copies: U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 1, No. 7. October 1993 (1, 12, 5)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 1, No. 5. August 1993 (1, 12, 5)
          - U.S. - Iran Review: Forum on American - Iranian Relations. Vol. 1, No. 2. May 1993 (1, 12, 5)
        Subseries 6: United Nations Report
      - United Nations Report (1, 12, 6)
        - (1, 12, 6)
          - Letter from Secretary - General to the President of the Security Council. 12/24/1991: Letter concerns the publication of the second and final report the United Nations endeavor to study the country reconstruction efforts and needs after conflict between Iran and Iraq. (1, 12, 6)
          - United Nations. Secretary General. Security Council. Report. 12/24/1991: Report compiled with aid of United Nations members on Iran and Iraq reconstruction: 1 - 58 (1, 12, 6)
          - United Nations. Secretary General. Security Council. Report. 12/24/1991: Further Report on the UN team visiting the Islamic Republic of Iran to study the reconstruction effort: 1 - 119 (1, 12, 6)
        Subseries 7: Rights in Iraq
      - Rights in Iraq (1, 12, 7)
        - (1, 12, 7)
          - Rights. Vol. 1, No. 2. Winter 1994 (1, 12, 7)
          - Rights. Vol. 1, No. 1. Fall 1993 (1, 12, 7)
        Subseries 8: NAMAH 1994
      - NAMAH 1994 (1, 12, 8)
        - (1, 12, 8)
          - NAMAH. Vol. 2, No. 2. Summer 1994. (1, 12, 8)
          - NAMAH. Vol. 2, No. 1. Spring 1994 (1, 12, 8)
        Subseries 9: MENAS Associates Iran Focus: Monthly News and Analysis of Economic, Political and Financial Developments in Iran 1988 - 1991
      - MENAS Associates Iran Focus: Monthly News and Analysis of Economic, Political and Financial Developments in Iran 1988 - 1991 (1, 12, 9)
        - (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 4, No. 11. December 1991 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 4, No. 10. November 1991 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 4, No. 2. February 1991 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 4, No. 1. January 1991 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 2, No. 8. September 1989 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 2, No. 2. February 1989 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 2, No. 1. February 1989 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 2, No. 1. January 1989 (1, 12, 9)
          - Iran Focus. Vol. 1, No. 3. December 1988 (1, 12, 9)
        Subseries 10: Iran Business Monitor 1994 - 1995
      - Iran Business Monitor 1994 - 1995 (1, 12, 10)
        - (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 4, No. 8. August 1995 (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 4, No. 7. July 1995 (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 4, No. 6. June 1995: two copies (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 4, No. 5. May 1995 (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 4, No. 4. April 1995 (1, 12, 10)
          - Iran Business Monitor. Vol. 3, No. 7. July 1994 (1, 12, 10)
        Subseries 11: Echo of Islam 1986
      - Echo of Islam 1986 (1, 12, 11)
        - (1, 12, 11)
          - …Victory is Ours. Echo of Islam. Vol. 6, No. 5. Sept., Oct. 1986 (Safar 1407) (1, 12, 11)
          - Hajj: The Ultimate Uprising. Echo of Islam. Vol. 6, No. 4. August 1986 (Muharram 1407) (1, 12, 11)
          - Desecrating Sacred Quds. Echo of Islam. Vol. 6, No. 3. July 1986 (Shawwal 1406) (1, 12, 11)
          - Journey of Light. Echo of Islam. Vol. 6, No. 1. April - May 1986 (Shaban 1406) (1, 12, 11)
          - Geneva Conference: Dividing The World. Echo of Islam. Vol. 5, No. 6. Dec. - Jan. 1986 (Rabiul - Thani 1406) (1, 12, 11)
        Subseries 12: Echo of Islam 1984
      - Echo of Islam 1984 (1, 12)
        - (1, 12)
          - Four Years of Imposed War. Echo of Islam. Vol. 4, No. 4. Sept./ Oct. 1984 (Muharram 1405) (1, 12)
          - Shoot Out Over the Persian Gulf. Echo of Islam. Vol. 4, No. 3. July/Aug. 1984 (1, 12)
          - Echo of Islam. Vol. 4, No. 1. Mar./Apr. 1984 (1, 12)
          - Lebanese Muslim Combatants: When The Gun is the Only Solution. Echo of Islam. Vol. 4, No. 2. Apr./May 1984 (1, 12)
        Subseries 13: Echo of Islam 1992 - 1993
      - Echo of Islam 1992 - 1993 (1, 12, 13)
        - (1, 12, 13)
          - Palestinian Nation: A Restless Volcano. Echo of Islam. Year 8, Serial No. 81 (1, 12, 13)
          - The Rebirth of Islam. Echo of Islam. No. 102 May 1993. (1, 12, 13)
          - The People Glorious Presence in Scene. Echo of Islam. No. 104, February 1993 (1, 12, 13)
          - Integration: A Common Need, A Divergent Response. Echo of Islam. June 1992. No. 96 (1, 12, 13)
          - Golden Policies of IMF in Developing Countries. Echo of Islam. No. 93, March 1992 (1, 12, 13)
        Subseries 14: Echo of Iran Index and Journals 1991
      - Echo of Iran Index and Journals 1991 (1, 12, 14)
        - (1, 12, 14)
          - 1991: The Echo of Iran Index (issues 1 - 12):1 - 11 (1, 12, 14)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 354, No. 12 (47). December 1991:1 - 36 (1, 12, 14)
          - Handwritten Note November 30, 1991 (1, 12, 14)
            - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 354, No. 11(46). November 1991: 1 - 30 (1, 12, 14)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 354, No. 5 (40). May 1991, with handwritten notes on the cover:1 - 30 (1, 12, 14)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 354, No. 3 (38). February 1991: 2 - 30 (1, 12, 14)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 355, No. 2 (37) February 1991: 1 - 30 (1, 12, 14)
        Subseries 15: Echo of Iran Journals 1990 - 1991
      - Echo of Iran Journals 1990 - 1991 (1, 12, 15)
        - (1, 12, 15)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 355, No. 1 (36). January 1991: 1 - 30 (1, 12, 15)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 343, No. 35. December 1990: 1 - 30 (1, 12, 15)
          - The Echo of Iran: An Independent and Objective Review of Iranian Affairs. Vol. 353, No. 34. November 1990 (1, 12, 15)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 353, No. 33. October 1990 (1, 12, 15)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 352, No. 31. July 1990 (1, 12, 15)
          - Handwritten note from J. Behrouz (?) requesting subscription of The Echo of Iran at William and Mary and paper written by James Bill. (1, 12, 15)
            - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 353, No. 30. June 1990 (1, 12, 15)
          - Letter from James Bill asking for subscription to The Echo of Iran and wishing recipient a Happy New Year (1, 12, 15)
            - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 352, No. 25. January 1990 (1, 12, 15)
        Subseries 16: Echo of Iran 1993
      - Echo of Iran 1993 (1, 12, 16)
        - (1, 12, 16)
          - 1993: The Echo of Iran Index (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 68. October 1993 (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 70. December 1993 (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 69. November 1993 (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 66. July 1993 (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 65. June 1993 (1, 12, 16)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 64. May 1993 (1, 12, 16)
        Subseries 17: Echo of Iran 1993/1992
      - Echo of Iran 1993/1992 (1, 12, 17)
        - (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 63. April 1993 (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 62. March 1993 (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 61. February 1993 (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 41, No. 60. January 1993 (1, 12, 17)
          - 1992: The Echo of Iran Index (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 40, No. 12(59). December 1992 (1, 12, 17)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 40, No. 11(58). November 1992 (1, 12, 17)
        Subseries 18: Echo of Iran 1992
      - Echo of Iran 1992 (1, 12, 18)
        - (1, 12, 18)
        Subseries 19: Echo of Iran 1994/1995
      - Echo of Iran 1994/1995 (1, 12, 19)
        - (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 83. February 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 82. January 1995 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 77. July 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 76. June 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 75. May 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 74. April 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 73. March 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 72. February 1994 (1, 12, 19)
          - The Echo of Iran. Vol. 42, No. 71. January 1994 (1, 12, 19)
        Subseries 20: Dialogue Newsletter Published by the Public Affairs Committee of Shia Muslims
      - Dialogue Newsletter Published by the Public Affairs Committee of Shia Muslims (1, 12, 20)
        - (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. October 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. September 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. August 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. June 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. May 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. April 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. March 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. February 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. December 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. January 1995 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Islam Beyond Cultural Distortions. Dialogue. September 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. August 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. July 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. May 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. April 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. March 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. February 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. January 1994 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. December 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. November 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. October 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. September 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. August 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. July 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. June 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. May 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - US - Iran Review. April 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. June 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. April 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. March 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. February 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - 2 Copies: Dialogue. January 1993 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. December 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. November 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. October 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. September 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. August 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. July 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. June 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. May 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. December/January 1992 (1, 12, 20)
          - Dialogue. November 1991 (1, 12, 20)
        Subseries 21: Daily Report
      - Daily Report (1, 12, 21)
        - (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: Majles Sessions, Election Results. 6/29/1993 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report: Near East and South Asia. 6/28/1993 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: Jun Majles Sessions. 7/23/1992 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: 20 - 29 Jan Majles Sessions: 2/28/1992 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: Majles Sessions. 1/31/1992 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: Majiles Sessions. 9/29/1992 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: Democratic Kurdistan Party Official Interviewed. 9/17/1992 (1, 12, 21)
          - Foreign Broadcast Information Service. Daily Report Supplement: Near East and South Asia. Iran: 9 April - 2 June 1991 Majiles Sessions. 7/9/1991 (1, 12, 21)
        Subseries 22: CIRA (Center for Iranian Research and Analysis) Newsletter 1990 - 1995
      - CIRA (Center for Iranian Research and Analysis) Newsletter 1990 - 1995 (1, 12, 22)
        - (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 10, No. 2. Winter 1995 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 9, No. 3. Summer 1994 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 9, No. 2. Winter 1994 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 8, No. 1 - 2. Fall 1992/Winter 1993 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 9, No. 1. Fall 1993 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 7, No. 1 - 2. Fall 1991/Winter 1992 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 6, No. 3. Spring/Summer 1991 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 6, No. 1. Fall 1990 (1, 12, 22)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 5, No. 3. Spring/Summer 1990 (1, 12, 22)
        Subseries 23: CIRA (Center for Iranian Research and Analysis) Newsletter 1987 - 1989
      - CIRA (Center for Iranian Research and Analysis) Newsletter 1987 - 1989 (1, 12, 23)
        - (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 4, No. 3. Winter 1989 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 5, No. 2. Fall 1989 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 5, No. 1. Spring/Summer 1989 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 3, No. 3. Winter 1988 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 4, No. 2. Fall 1988 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 4, No. 1. Spring/Summer 1988 (1, 12, 23)
          - CIRA Newsletter. Vol. 3, No. 2. Fall 1987 (1, 12, 23)
        Subseries 24: Arabia Monitor
      - Arabia Monitor (1, 12, 24)
        - (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 8. August 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 7. July 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 5. May 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 6. June 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 4. April 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 3. March 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 2. February 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 1. January 1993 (1, 12, 24)
          - 2 Copies: Arabia Monitor. Vol. 1, No. 7. August 1992 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 1, No. 6. July 1992 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol.1, No. 4/5. May - June 1992 (1, 12, 24)
          - Arabia Monitor. Vol. 1, No. 2/3. March - April 1992 (1, 12, 24)
    Subseries 2: Articles written By James Bill
  - Articles written By James Bill (2)
    - (2, 13)
        Subseries 1: Journals with Articles written by James Bill
      - Journals with Articles written by James Bill (2, 13, 1)
        - (2, 13, 1)
          - The Politics of Extremism in Iran. Current History: A World Affairs Journal. January, 1982: 9+ (2, 13, 1)
          - The Challenge of Change: Petroleum and Planning in the Middle East. ed. Alice Taylor. Focus from The American Geographic Society. Vol. 22, No. 1. September 1971:1+ (2, 13, 1)
          - Bill, James and John Alden Williams. Shii Islam and Roman Catholicism: A Comparative Analysis. New Catholic World. November/December 1988: 274 (2, 13, 1)
          - Power Politics and Shiism. Harvard International Review. Vol. 6, No. 7. May/June 1984:14+ (2, 13, 1)
          - The New Iran: Relations With Its Neighbors and the United States. Asian Update. The Asian Society. August 1991. (2, 13, 1)
          - Islam: Misunderstood Throughout The World. The Fountain. January/March 2001: 30+ (2, 13, 1)
          - William and Mary Alumni Magazine. Alumni Association. Spring/Summer 2003 (2, 13, 1)
        Subseries 2: Articles written by James Bill
      - Articles written by James Bill (2, 13)
        - (2, 13)
          - Iran and the United States: A Clash of Hegemonies. Middle East Report. No. 212, Vol. 29, No. 3. Fall 1999: 44+ (2, 13)
          - Iran: The Prodigal Returns. World Monitor: The Christian Science Monitor Monthly. Vol. 2, No. 3. March 1989: 64+ (2, 13)
          - Prospering Persia: Modern Mecca. Finance: The Magazine of Money. Vol. 93, No. 1. January 1975: 21+ (2, 13)
          - Bill, James and Dr. Carl Leiden. The Rebirth of Islam. Ashland Now. Vol. 3, No. 2. Summer 1979: 8 (2, 13)
          - The Unfinished Revolution in Iran. International Insight. Vol. 2, No. 1. November/December, 1981: 6+ (2, 13)
        Subseries 3: Middle East Insight Magazine with Articles by James Bill
      - Middle East Insight Magazine with Articles by James Bill (2, 13, 3)
        - (2, 13, 3)